Romania Subject Files, Inclusive: 1936-2008, undated, Bulk: 1974-1991
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- General, 1961-2006, undated; 1
  - Culture, 1965-1990, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Literature (1 of 2), 1964-1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Literature (2 of 2), 1977-1990, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Individual Writers, 1975-1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Art. Architecture. Music., 1970-2006, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Architecture. Restoration, 1976-1986 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Women, 1975-1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Children and Youth, 1976-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Society. Family. Everyday life. (1 of 2), 1964-1976, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Society. Family. Everyday life. (2 of 2), 1977-1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Art ( 1of 2), 1966-1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Art (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Transylvania, 1980-1989, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Hungarian Minority, 1987-1990, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Demolitions in Bucharest (1 of 2), 1983-1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Demolitions in Bucharest (2 of 2), 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Rural Development Policy - Systematization (1 of 4), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Rural Development Policy - Systematization (2 of 4), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Rural Development Policy. Systematization (3 of 4), 1989 June-December (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Rural Development Policy. Systematization (4 of 4), 1990, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - State Desecration, Demolition of Church Buildings, 1984-1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Architecture. Restoration. Preservation, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - National Salvation Front, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (1 of 9), 1990 June (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (2 of 9), 1991 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (3 of 9), 1992 November-December (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (4 of 9), 1993 January-February (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (5 of 9), 1993 March-April (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (6 of 9), 1993 May-June (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (7 of 9), 1993 July-August (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (8 of 9), 1993 September (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Adevarul. Clippings (9 of 9), 1993 October-November (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (1 of 26), 1988 January-June (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (2 of 26), 1988 July-December (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (3 of 26), 1989 January-June (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (4 of 26), 1989 July-November (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (5 of 26), 1989 December 1-22 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (6 of 26), 1989 December 23-27 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (7 of 26), 1989 December 28-31 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (8 of 26), 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (9 of 26), 1990 January 1-9 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (10 of 26), 1990 January 10-31 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (11 of 26), 1990 February (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (12 of 26), 1990 March (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (13 of 26), 1990 April (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (14 of 26), 1990 May 1-15 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (15 of 26), 1990 May 16-31 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (16 of 26), 1990 June (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (1 of 10), 1988 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (2 of 10), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (3 of 10), 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (4 of 10), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (5 of 10), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (6 of 10), 1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (7 of 10), 1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (8 of 10), 1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (9 of 10), 1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Summary of World Broadcasts (10 of 10), 1997 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (17 of 26), 1990 July-September (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (18 of 26), 1990 October-December (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (19 of 26), 1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (20 of 26), 1992 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (21 of 26 ), 1993 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (22 of 26), 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (23 of 26), 1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (24 of 26), 1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (25 of 26), 1997 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Press. Articles (26 of 26), 1998-2000 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports ( 1 of 3), 1974 September-December (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports ( 2 of 3), 1975 January-December (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports ( 3 of 3), 1978 June-1988 January, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Background Reports ( 1 of 2), 1979 November-1980 July (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Background Reports ( 2 of 2), 1981 January-1982 March (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports. Earthquake., 1977 Mart-April (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports. Culture, 1975 October-1979 June (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports. Literature., 1974 November-1978 March (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports. Agriculture. Economy. Labor., 1975 September-1978 June (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Radio Free Europe Research. Romania. Situation Reports. Protests. Democratic Movement., 1977 February-1979 May (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Romanian Revolution, 1989 December-1990 January (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - General (1 of 20), 1965-1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - General (2 of 20), 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - General (3 of 20), 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - General (4 of 20), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - General (5 of 20), 1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - General (6 of 20), 1990 January-February (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - General (7 of 20), 1990 March-May (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - General (8 of 20), 1990 June-November (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - General (9 of 20), 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - General (10 of 20), 1992 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - General (11 of 20), 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - General (12 of 20), 1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - General (13 of 20), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - General (14 of 20), 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - General (15 of 20), 1998 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - General (16 of 20), 1999 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - General (17 of 20), 2000 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - General (18 of 20), 2001 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - General (19 of 20), undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - General. Typescripts (20 of 20), undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Romania Libera. Articles (1 of 2), 1990 March-December (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Romania Libera. Articles (2 of 2), 1991 January-April (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Scinteia. Articles (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Scinteia. Articles (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Press. Articles, 1987 May-December (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Denominational, 1936-2008, undated; 2
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Denominational Romania subject files contain categories similar to the general subject files with the focus on a particular denomination and individual prosecution cases of believers and clergy.
  - Adventist Church, 1970-2002, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Individual Adventists. Buzdugan, Ion (1 of 2), 1955-1958 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Individual Adventists. Buzdugan, Ion (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Individual Adventists. Catarama, Dorel (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Individual Adventists. Catarama, Dorel (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Individual Adventists. Dragomir, Mircea, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Anglican Church, 1974-1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Armenian Church, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Church, 1980-2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Church History, 1967-1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Individual Baptists. Capusan, Radu, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Individual Baptists. Gogu, Constantin, S, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Individual Baptists. Moravu, Stefan, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Individual Baptists. Nicolescu, Pavel, 1972-1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Individual Baptists. Olah, Liviu, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Individual Baptists. Osvath, Ludovic, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Individual Baptists. Popa, Doru, 1987 1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Individual Baptists. Popescu, Aurel, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Individual Baptists. Popescu, Nestor, 1983-1989 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Individual Baptists. Sfatcu, Constantin, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Individual Baptists. Talos, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Baptist Church Administration, 1976-1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - List of Baptist Churches, 1977-1993 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Individual Baptist Churches, 1975-1989 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Baptist Church Leadership, 1976-1988 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - The 1977 Baptist Church Congress, 1972-1977 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Decisions taken by the 1977 Baptist Church Congress, 1976-1979 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Baptist Church. State. Law, 1976-1989 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Baptist Church-State Relations, 1974-1983 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Baptist Church Legislation, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Reopening of Baptist Churches, 1968-1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Registration of Baptist Churches, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Oppressive Practices toward Baptist Believers, 1971-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Harassment of Baptist Believers, 1977-1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Physical Assault and Murder of Baptist Believers, 1979-1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Fines of Baptist Believers, 1979-1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Interrogations of Baptist Believers, 1982-1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Trials of Baptist Believers, 1979-1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Imprisonment and Exile of Baptist Believers, 1977-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - State Interference in Baptist Church Affairs, 1977-1985 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - State Interference in Baptist Union Level Administration, 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Legal Disabilities of Baptist Church. Refusal of Registration and Closure, 1983-1999 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - State Interference in Baptist Church’s Parish Level Administration, 1978-1986 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - State Interference in Affairs of Baptist Clergy and Hierarchy, 1979-1993 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Materials Relating to Baptist Church Religious and Theological Education, 1976-1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Materials Relating to Baptist Church Religious Literature, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - State Expropriation, Desecration or Demolition of Baptist Church Buildings, 1978-1989 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Discrimination of Baptist Believers in Employment, 1977-1987 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Discrimination of Baptist Believers in Education, 1976-1985 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry toward Baptist Believers, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Attacks on Baptist Church in the Media, 1976-1982 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Baptist Believers House Searches. Confiscation of Literature, 1982-1987 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Baptist Church Life, 1977-1984 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Baptist Church Festivals and Anniversaries, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Baptist Services. Rituals. Liturgy, 1974-1987 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Baptist Church Modernization, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Baptist Church Preaching. Conversions. Evangelism, 1976-1989 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Baptist Church Official Publications, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Baptist Church Official Publications. Crestinul Azi (Christian Today), 1992 May-June (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Baptist Church Official Publications. Indrumatorul Crestin Baptist (Christian Baptist Guide), 1977-1991 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Baptist Church Revival. Charismatic Renewal, 1980-1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Baptist Church Excommunications, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Baptist Church Philanthropy, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Baptist Church Clergy. Priesthood, 1978-1991, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Hierarchy of Baptist Clergy, 1976-1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Clergy Ordination, Retirement. Election. Death, etc., 1975-1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Individual Baptist Clergy, 1975-1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Individual Baptist Clergy. Negrut, Paul, 1990, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Individual Baptist Clergy. Ton, Josif, 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Individual Baptist Clergy. Ton, Josif, 1979-1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Working and Living Conditions of Baptist Clergy, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Statistics, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Church’s International Contacts. Aid. Solidarity, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Western Reactions to Baptist Church Situation. Demonstrations. Protest Actions. Aid, etc., 1936-1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Baptist Contacts with International Organizations, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Peace Activities of Baptist Church, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Baptist Visits to and From Other Countries, 1968-1985, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Baptist Activities Disapproved by the State, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Baptist Protests, 1975-1986 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Defense of Baptist Believers' Rights, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Baptist Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1977-1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Baptist Contacts with Foreigners, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Baptist Theology, 1975-1996, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Theological Education, 1976-1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Religious Education of Children, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Unity-Schisms-Cults, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Statistics, 1968-1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Relations with Fellow Believers, 1968-1987 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Baptist Involvement in Secular Affairs and Politics, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Art, Architecture, Music, Literature, 1979-1987 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Bibles, 1974-1987, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Baptist Youth and Children, 1977 1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Sociology. Baptist Family, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Brethren Church, 1975-1987 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Evangelical church, 1965-2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Congress of Evangelical Alliance of Romania, 1990 October 19-21 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Islam, 1968-1990 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1955-1996 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Judaism, 1958-1968 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Judaism, 1979-2001 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - History of Judaism in Romania, 1977-2001 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Individuals. Ann-Mari Behrman, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Community-State Relations, 1978-1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Oppressive Practices toward Jewish Believers, 1978-1987, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Religious Life of Jewish Community, 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Chief Rabbi Rosen, Moses, 1978-1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Community's International Relations, 1978-1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Delegations' Visits to Jewish Communities, 1978-1987 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Emigration of Jewish Believers on Religious Grounds, 1976-2000 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Community Statistics, 1976-1987, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Judaism and National Identity. Anti-Semitism, 1984-1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Art. Architecture. Literature. Music, 1976 1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sociological Surveys, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lutheran Church, 1965-1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Individual Lutheran Churches, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Oppressive Practices toward Lutheran Believers and Clergy, 1977-1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Lutheran Church Life, 1977-1987 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Lutheran Clergy. Priesthood, 1985-1986, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Lutheran Church's International Relations, 1976-1989 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Lutheran Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Lutheran Theological Education, 1979-1983 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Lutheran Statistics, 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Lutheran Relations with Fellow Believers, 1986-2000 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Lutheran Faith and National Identity, 1978-1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Lutheran Literature, 1984-1989 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Masons, 1985-1990, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Old Believers, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Lord's Army (Oastea Domnului), 1970-1993 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Lord's Soldier (Ostasul Domnului), 1935 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - History of Lord's Army, 1975-1979 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Individual Lord's Army Believers. Dorz, Traian, 1982-1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Oppressive practices toward Lord's Army Members, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Individual Lord's Army Clergy. Trifa, Iosif, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - International Relations, 1973-1983 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Orthodox Church, 1981-2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Orthodox Church History, 1929-2003 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Believers, 1981-2004 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Orthodox Church Administration, 1975-1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - List of Orthodox Churches, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Churches, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Orthodox Canon Law, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Orthodox Church Finances, 1961-1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Orthodox Church Patriarchate, 1974-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Orthodox Church Sobor, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Orthodox Church Dioceses, 1977-1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Orthodox Church. State. Law, 1990, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Orthodox Church-State Relations, 1967-1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Orthodox Church Legislation, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Opening and Consecration of Orthodox Churches, 1970-1980s (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Orthodox Church Commendation in Secular Press, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Oppressive Practices toward Orthodox Believers, 1971-2004 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Harassment of Orthodox Believers, 1979-1985 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Physical Assault and Murder of Orthodox Believers, 1975-1987 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Orthodox Believers Fines, 1979-1986 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Imprisonment and Exile of Orthodox Believers, 1979-1986 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Legal Disabilities of Orthodox Church. Refusal of Registration and Closure of Churches, 1983-1987 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Oppressive Practices in Affairs of Clergy and Hierarchy, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Infiltration into Orthodox Church, 1985-2000 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Oppressive Practices Relating to Orthodox Religious Literature, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - State Expropriations, Desecration and Demolition of Orthodox Church Buildings, 1977-2000 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Misuse of Psychiatry toward Orthodox Believers, 1979-1986 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Orthodox Believers' House Searches. Confiscation of Religious Literature, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Orthodox Church Life, 1977-1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Orthodox Festivals and Anniversaries, 1965-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Services. Rituals. Liturgy, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Orthodox Church Modernization. Attitude and Action, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Orthodox Pilgrimages. Holy Places, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Orthodox Preaching. Conversions. Evangelism, 1920-1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Orthodox Parish life, 1975-1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Defection from Orthodox Faith, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Secularization of Orthodox Church, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Official Publications, 1961-1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Orthodox Revival. Charismatic Renewal, 1955-1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Orthodox Monasticism, 1966-1999 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Orthodox Church Philanthropy, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Orthodox Clergy. Priesthood, 1976-1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Orthodox Church Hierarchy, 1972-1991 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Orthodox Clergy Ordination. Retirement. Election. Death, etc., 1962-1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy, 1971-1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Ambrus-Cernat, Emeric, 1980s (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Arapasu, Teoctist, 1977-2008 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Boboc, Ion, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Calciu-Dumitreasa, Gheorghe (1 of 2), 1978-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Calciu-Dumitreasa, Gheorghe (2 of 2), 1984-2007 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Cleopa, Ilie, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Gafton, Lucian, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Gaga, Doru Aurel, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Galaction, Gala, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Galeriu, Constantin, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Gavrila, Stefan, 1974-1977 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Maftei, Costica, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Marina, Patriarch Justinian, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Mladin, Nicolae, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Moisescu, Patriarch Justin, 1977-1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Negoita, Liviu, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Pescaru, Natanael, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Pop, Alexandru, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Staniloae, Dumitru, 1981-1993 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Individual Orthodox Clergy. Trifa, Valerian, 1980-1987 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Orthodox Clergy and Priesthood Statistics, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Orthodox Church's International Contacts. Solidarity. Aid, 1975-1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Western Reactions to Orthodox Church Situation. Demonstrations, etc., 1954-1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Orthodox Church's Contacts with International Organizations, 1972-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Orthodox Church Visits Abroad, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Visits to Orthodox Church from Foreign Delegations, 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Activities of Orthodox Church Disapproved by State. General, 1973-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Activities of Orthodox Church Disapproved by State. Meetings. Prayer groups. Rites. Ceremonies. Services, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Activities of Orthodox Church Disapproved by State. Individuals, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Activities of Orthodox Church Disapproved by State. Public demonstrations, protests, 1977-1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Activities of Orthodox Church Disapproved by State. Defense of believers' rights, 1982-1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Believers Criticism of Orthodox Church Policy, 1981-1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Defection of Orthodox Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Orthodox Believers' Contact with Foreigners, Emigres, etc., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Orthodox Church Theology. Philosophy. Education. Morality, 1969-1991 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Orthodox Theology, 1948-1987 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Individual Orthodox Theologians, 1973-1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Orthodox Philosophy, 1976-1982 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Orthodox Ethics and Morality, 19707, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Orthodox Theological Education, 1975-1989 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Orthodox Church Philosophy of Unity, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)